Guide to the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences Records SC1055
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-289
  - Devine, Robert A., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Domar, Evsey, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Dror, Yehezkel, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Fogelman, Edwin, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Garraty, John, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Halewood, William H., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Hall, K.R.L., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Ham, George C., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Hammel, Eugene A., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Harbison, Fred H., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Hoenigwald, Henry M., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Holtzman, Wayne H., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Hurewitz, J.C., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Jackson, Philip W., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Jay, Phyllis, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Kaufman, Arnold S., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Kohler, I., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Madsen, William, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Manuel, Frank E., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Messick, Samuel J., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Millon, Rene, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Mizuhara, H., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Mosteller, Frederick, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Myers, Charles A., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Paul, Benjamin, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Poggioli, Renato, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Rangell, Leo, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Reynolds, Vernon, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Rogers, Carl R., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Sacks, Howard, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Scarf, Herbert, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Schaller, George B., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Schapiro, Meyer, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Sindler, Allen Paul, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Smith, John H., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Trager, George L., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Uttley Albert M., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Washburn, Sherwood L., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Whyte, Lancelot L., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Wilensky, Harold L., 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Wright, Gordon, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Summer Conference List, 1962, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Primate Behavior Conference, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Cognitive Learning Cronbach-Carrnegie, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Activities of Fellows 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Fellows, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Fellows, 1963-64 [handwritten] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Alpert, Harry, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Atkinson, Richard C., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Wendell, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Bergson, Abram, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bohannon, Paul J., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Bolt, Richard A., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Bouwsma, William J., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Bracher, Karl D., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Burling, Robbins, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Coleman, James S., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Cronbach, Lee J., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Elioseff, Lee Andrew, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Fishman, Joshua A., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Gay, Peter A., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Gershoy, Leo, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Gibson, James J., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Gibson, Eleanor J., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Haugen, Einar, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Hempel, Carl, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Kay, Herma Hill (Schreter), 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Landaur, Thomas K., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Keislar, Evan, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Linz, Juan, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Lounsbury, Floyd G., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Mahl, George F., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - May, Ernest, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Nader, Laura, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Price, Daniel O., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Pye, Lucian W., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Quarton, Gardner C., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Reissman, Leonard, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Rosenfield. Claire, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Sahlins, Marshall, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Savage, Leonard Jimmie, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Scott, J. P., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Seton-Watson, George, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Shaffer, Jerome A., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Sinha, Surajit, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Stone, Julius, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Thompson, William R., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Tiedeman, David V., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Tyhurst, James, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Verba, Sidney, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Ward, John W., 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Wohwill, Joachim, 1963-64 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - 1964-65 Inventories (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Fellows 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Psycho-Linguistics/Cutting Edge 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Baerends, Gerald P., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Baklanoff, Eric N., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Barnett, Homer, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Bellah, Robert, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Black, Max, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Bloch, Bernard, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Bourricaud, Francois, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Norman O., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Cooper, Franklin S., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Erikson, Erik, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Fodor, Jerry, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Gallino, Luciano, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Ginsburg, Benson E., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Goldschmidt, Walter, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Greenberg, Joseph H., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Greenstein, Fred I., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Jenkins, James J., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Kirk, Dudley, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Knapp, Peter, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Koestler, Arthur, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Konvitz, Milton R., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Kusch, P., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Lambert, Wallace, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Lammers, Donald Ned, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Laughlin, William S., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - LeGuin, Charles C., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Leontief, Wassily, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Liberman, Alvin M., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Matthews, Donald R., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Maybury-Lewis, David, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Mills, Theodore M., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Mishkin, Paul, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Nagel, Stuart S., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Pop, Mihai, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Rimland, Bernard, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Rogat, Y., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Seeley, John R., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Smith, M. Brewster, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Tucker, Robert C., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Yohe, William P., 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Zwerdling, Alex, 1964-65 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Fellows 1965-1966, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Inventories of Interest, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Activities of the Fellows, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Abelson, Robert, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Ernest W., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Alston, William P., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Beidelman, Thomas, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Bevan, William, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Bicanic, Rudolf, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Brosin, Henry W., 1965-66; 1955-56 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Campbell, Donald, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Carstairs, G. M., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Caspari, Ernst, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Cohn, Norman R. C., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Crews, Frederick C., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - D'Andrade, Roy G., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Dunkel, Harold B., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Etzioni, Amitai, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Ferrarotti, Franco, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Fischer, John L., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Golde, Peggy, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Green, Bert F., Jr., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Guiart, Jean, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Harrison, Frank L., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Harsanyi, John C., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Harvey, O. J., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Higham, John, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Hoffman, Stanley, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Holland, John L., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Husen, Torsten, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Johansson, K. Gunnar E., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Kay, Paul, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Lidz, Theodore, M.D., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - McGuire. William J., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Mandelbaum, Seymour, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Metzger, Duane, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Newcomb, Theodore, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - O'Connell, Kenneth J., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Reich, Donald R., 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Rheinstein, Max, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Rommetveit, Ragnar, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Schorske, Carl, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Seiler, Hansjakob, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Stanley, Julian C., 1965-66/1966-67 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Stein, Herbert, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Tannenbaum, Percy, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Thimme, Annelise, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Trow, Martin, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Uhlenbeck, Eugenius, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Watson, Richard A., 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Weinreich, Uriel, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Consistency Theory, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Inventories of Interests, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Aaron, Benjamin, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Aronfreed, Justin, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Beattie, J. H. M., 1959-60/1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Cook, Albert S., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Daalder, Hans, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Dahl, Robert, 1955-56, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Dias, Jorge, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Eckstein, Otto, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Gray, Hanna H., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Gurley, John G., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Gutman, Herbert G., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Hahn, Frank, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Hess, Robert D., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Hexter, Jack, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Hill, Winfred F., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Hobbs, Nicholas, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Hofstadter, Albert, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Henry, Jules, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Jensen, Arthur, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Kaufman, I. Charles, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Kelman, Herbert, 1954-55/1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Litwak, Eugene, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Lorwin, Val, 1961-62/1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Lowenthal, Leo, 1955-56/1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Lydall, Harold F., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Macaulay, Stewart, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - McBride, Glen, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Meisner, Maurice, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Mitchell, William, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Olmsted, David, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Riggs, Fred, 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Rokkan, Stein, 1959-60,1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Rosenberg, Hans W., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Scheflen, Albert E., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Schneider, David M., 1966-67 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1960-61/1966-67 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Singer, Robert, 1966-67 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Smedslund, Jan, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Tajfel, Henri, 1966-67 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Watkins, Calvert W., 1966-67 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - West, Louis J., 1966-67 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Inventory of Professional Interests, 1967-68 Fellows (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Inventories, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Abrams, Meyer, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Ainsworth, Mary D. S., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Alker, Hayward R., Jr., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Astin, Alexander W., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Baron, Hans, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Binder, Leonard, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Bloomfield, Morton W., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Bradley, Philip B., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Brody, Richard, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Broudy, Harry S., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Brown, Frederick G., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Cohn, Bernard, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Colson, Elizabeth, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Diebold, A. Richard, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Dupree, A. Hunter, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Eisner, Robert, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Emery, Frederick E., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Firth, Roderick, 1964-65/1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Fortes, Meyer, 1958-59/1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Frake, Charles, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - French, David, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Gluckman, Max, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Haas, Mary R., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Hamburg, David, 1956-57/1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Ikeuchi, Hajime, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Jerison, Harry J., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Kadish, Sanford, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Larson, O. F., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Laslett, Peter, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Lerner, I. Michael, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Levy, Robert J., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - MacRae, Donald G., 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Morris, Clarence, 1957-58; 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Price, Hugh Douglas, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Rubinstein, Eli, 1967-68 (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Sabshin, Melvin, 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Sills, David, 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Sleigh, Robert C., Jr., 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Thomas C., 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Steinberg, Ira, 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Szczepanski, Jan, 1960-61/1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Vickrey, William, 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Vlastos, Gregory, 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Wittrock, Merlin C., 1967-68 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Inventories of Interests, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Inventories of Interests 2, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Almond, Gabriel, 1956-57/1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Norman, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Barber, James D., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Berlin, Brent, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Birdwhistell, Ray L., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Crook, John H., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Dodwell, Peter C., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Erikson, Kai T., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Falk, Richard A., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Frankena, William K., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Franklin, Marc A., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Glickman, Stephen E., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Himmelstrand, Ulf, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Hirschman, Albert O., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Howe, Irving, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Koopmans, Tjalling C., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Kothari, Rajni, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Lipson, Leon, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Lowenthal, Richard, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Maccoby, Michael, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Masserman, Jules H., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Malcolm, Norman, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Montias, John Michael, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Moscovici, Serge, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Mussen, Paul H., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Noyes, Pierre H., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Paret, Peter, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Peel, Edwin A., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Peterson, Merrill D., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Pike, Kenneth L., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Plantinga, Alvin C., 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Potter, David, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Riesman, David, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Rilay, Gresham (Visiting Scholar), 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Safran, Nadav, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Sears, Robert R., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Sears, Pauline S., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Shultz, George P., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Stone, Phillip, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Tambiah, Stanley J., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Van De Geer, John P., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Ward, Robert E., 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Young, Frank, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Zelditch, Morris, 1968-69 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Inventories, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Bandura, Albert, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Barber, C. L., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Becker, Howard S., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Bolinger, Dwight L., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Brandt, Richard, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Braun, Rudolf, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Bunzel, Jack, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Cohen, Bernard C., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Cunningham, Luverne, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Davidson, Donald H., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Davis, John A., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Dedijer, Stevan, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Dimock, Edward, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Donald, David, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Flanders, Ned A., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Flavell, John, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Foster, George M., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Freedman, Ronald, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Freund, Paul A., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Gibbs, James, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Glaser, Robert, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Gorecki, Jan, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Grossman, Gregory, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Gunther, Gerald, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Huntington, Samuel P., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Kendler, Howard H., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Lewis, Harold, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Lilly, John, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Maccoby, Eleanor, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Mitchell, J. Clyde, 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Parker, Edwin B., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Phelps, Edmund S., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Pole, Jack R., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rawls, John, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Reitman, Walter, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Rorty, Amelie O., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Shneidman, Edwin S., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Short, James F., 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Skinner, G. William, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Small, Melvin, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Tax, Sol, 1968-69 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Von Wright, Johan M., 1969-70 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Wolin, Sheldon S., 1969-70 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Inventories of Interests, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Anthony, E. J., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Belsley, David A., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Bellack, Arno A., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Berkowitz, Leonard, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Bickel, Alexander, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Adelman, Irma, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Ajayi, Jacob F. A., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Cancian, Francesca M., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Cancian, Frank, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Condominas, Georges, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Conger, John J., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Costa-Pinto, Luiz, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Easterlin, Richard A., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Epstein, Leon D., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Fagen, Richard R., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Ferguson, Charles, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Fillmore, Charles, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Gillcrist, Thomas J., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Gillispie, Charles C., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Glaser, Robert J., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Gray, Charles M., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Hill, Reuben, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Hintikka, K. Jaakko, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Kruskal, William H., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Kunkel, John H., 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Manne, Alan, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Mendelshn, Gerald, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Morse, Richard, 1970-71 (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Savage, I. Richard, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Scheiber, Harry N., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Shimkin, Demitri B., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Sommers, Joseph, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Srinivas, M. N., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Steinberg, Erwin R., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Takala, Annika M., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Takala, Martti I., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Tversky, Amos, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Turner, Christy G., 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Wallerstein, Immanuel, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Wheeler, Stanton, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Wikler, Abraham, 1970-71 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Inventories of Interest, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Bettelheim, Bruno, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Boothe, Bert E., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Burks, Arthur W., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Cardona, George, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Cremin, Lawrence A., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Danelski, David J., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Davenport, William H., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Dershowitz, Alan M., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Fischer, Wolfram, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Fox, James, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Frey, Frederick W., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Germani, Gino, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Glazer, Nathan, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Gluckman, Max, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Goodlad, John I., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Green, David E., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Hartz, Louis, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Hodge, Robert W., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Jensen, Robert E., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Charles O., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Kenen, Peter B., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Kesner, Raymond P., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Lakoff, George, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Lakoff, Robin, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Leiserson, Michael, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - LeVine, Robert A., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Lindzey, Gardner, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Loehlin, John C., 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Mack, Maynard, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Mansfield, Edwin, 1971-72 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Newman, Frederick L., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Nozick, Robert, 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Pitelka, Frank A., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Riecken, Henry W., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Sartori, Giovanni, 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Schnore, Leo F., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Shepard, Roger N., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Spuhler, James N., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Stunkard, Albert J., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Sutherland, Sir Gordon, 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Walzer, Michael, 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Wiley, David E., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Wilson, Monica, 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Zimbardo, Philip G., 1971-72 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Theodore W., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Baxter, William F., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Boudon, Raymond, 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Bower, Gardon H., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Carlsson, Costa, 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Chipman, John S., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Cohen, Percy S., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Cooley, William W., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Davis, David B., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Gagne, Robert M., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Genovese, Eugene D., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Hall, John W., 1972-73 (Box 62, Folder 26)